Guide to the Sam Stark Scrapbook Collection, 1860-1950
Department of Special Collections
Stark, Samuel. Theatre scrapbook collection.,
1860-1950
M0622
Samuel Stark
28.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
19th century American and British stage material: photographs of 19th and early 20th century American and British actors, Irish Theatre programs, American silent film, and film and stage personalities.
Administrative Information
Access
None.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Samuel Stark.
Provenance
Collection started by Stark's mother and aunt. Stark's paternal grandmother was the sister of Joseph Schurmann of Holland, a French impressario who brought Bernhardt, Duse, and Patti to the U.S. The core collection came to Stark on his mother's death in 1936, and he built on it through additional gifts and purchases.
Biography
Authority on the history of the theatre, particularly American theatre, and collector of theatre photographs and ephemera.
Collection Scope and Content Summary
19th century American and British stage material: photographs of 19th and early 20th century American and British actors, Irish Theatre programs, American silent film, and film and stage personalities.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Jefferson, Joseph, 1829-1905.; Booth, Edwin, 1833-1893.; Terry, Ellen, Dame, 1847-1928.; Stanford, Jane Lathrop, 1828-1905.; Shearer, Norma, 1900-; Power, Tyrone, 1914-; Lombard, Carole, 1908-1942.; Barthelmess, Richard, 1895-1963.; Cooper, Jackie, 1922-; Allister, Claude, 1891-1970.; Dressler, Marie, 1869-1934.; Georgi, Yvonne.; Kreutzberg, Harald, 1902-1968.; Coward, Noel, 1899-1973.; Greene, Patterson.; Chekhov, Anton Pavlovich, 1860-1904.; Runyon, Damon, 1880-1946.; Allen, Viola.; Anglin, Margaret, 1876-1958.; Barrymore, John, 1882-1942.; Barrymore, John, 1878-1954.; Barrymore, Ethel, 1879-1959.; Benny, Jack, 1894-1974.; Bernhardt, Sarah, 1844-1923.; Burke, Billy, 1885-1970.; Cagney, James, 1899-1986.; Castle, Irene, 1893-1969.; Chaplin, Charlie, 1889-1977.; Cohan, George M., (George Michael), 1878-1942.; Davis, Bette, 1908-; Dressler, Marie, 1869-1934.; Epenscheid, Gertrude E., (Gertrude Elliot).; Fairbanks, Douglas, 1883-1939.; Farrar, Geraldine, 1882-1967.; Fiske, Minnie Madden, 1865-1932.; Frederick, Pauline, 1885-1938.; Gable, Clark, 1901-1960.; Gish, Lillian, 1893-1993.; Held, Anna, 1877?-1918.; Marlowe, Julia, 1865-1950.; Moore, Victor, 1876-1962.; Nazimova, Alla, 1879-1945.; Pickford, Mary, 1892-1979.; Russell, Lillian, 1861-1922.; Starr, Frances.; Stewart, Anita, 1895-1961.; Swanson, Gloria.; Talmadge, Constance, 1898-1973.; Talmadge, Norma, 1897-1957.; Tanguay, Eva, 1878-1947.; Valentino, Rudolph, 1895-1926.; West, Mae.; Ade, George, 1866-1944.; Armstrong, Paul, 1869-1915.; Ballard, Frederick, 1884-1957.; Barry, Tom, 1884-1931.; Boucicault, Dion, 1820-1890.; Broadhurst, George H., 1866-1945.; Browne, Porter Emerson, 1879-1934.; Craven, Frank, 1875-1945.; Crothers, Rachel, 1878-1958.; Davis, Owen, 1874-1956.; DeMille, William C.,q(William Churchill), 1878-1955.; Fitch, Clyde, 1865-1909.; Forbes, James, 1871-1938.; Gates, Eleanor, 1875-1951.; Gillette, William, 1853-1937.; Hopwood, Avery, 1882-1928.; Howard, Bronson, 1842-1908.; Hughes, Rupert, 1872-1956.; Kenyon, Charles, 1880-1961.; Kester, Paul, 1870-1933.; Klein, Charles, 1867-1915.; Knoblauch, Edward, 1874-1945.; MacKaye, Percy, 1875-1956.; Manners, J. Hartley.; Mayo, Margaret, 1882-1951.; Megrue, Roi Cooper, 1883-1927.; Mitchell, Langdon Elwyn, 1862-1935.; Montgomery, James, 1882-1966.; Moody, William Vaughn, 1869-1910.; Moore, Carlyle, 1909-1977.; Moore, Martha, 1865-1925.; Nirdlinger, Charles Frederic.; Parker, Lottie Blair.; Paulton, Harry, 1842-1917.; Peabody, Josephine Preston, 1874-1922.; Peple, Edward, 1869-1924.; Presbrey, Eugene W., (Eugene Wiley), 1853-1931.; Rosenfeld, Sydney, 1855-1931.; Royle, Edwin Milton, 1862-1942.; Sayre, Theodore Burt.; Scarborough, George Adolphus, 1859-1900.; Selwyn, Edgar, 1875-1944.; Shipman, Louis Evan, 1869-1933.; Tarkington, Booth, 1869-1946.; Thomas, A. E., (Albert Ellsworth), 1872-1947.; Thomas, Augustus, 1857-1934.; Tully, Richard Walton, 1877-1945.; Walter, Eugene, 1874-1941.; Bates, Blanche.; Coleman, Ronald.; Friganza, Trixie.; Gray, Gilda.; Mannering, Mary.; May, Edna.; Ring, Blanche.; Templeton, Fay.; Fields, Weber C.; Anspacker, Louis.; Barry, Phillip.; Bartholomae, Philip.; Buchanan, Thompson.; Caldwell, Anne.; Carpenter, Edward Childs.; Clarke, Joseph I. C.; Davis, Richard H.; Dodd, Lee Wilson.; Ellis, Edith.; Goodman, Jules E.; Hutton, Frederick.; Hazelton, George.; Hoyt, Charles.; Howard, Sidney.; Hurlburt, William.; Kennedy, Charles R.; Long, John L.; McClellan, C. S. M.; Middleton, George.; Patterson, Joseph.; Paulson, Edward.; Reid, James.; Ryley, M. C.; Sheldon, Edward.; Sutherland, Evelyn.; Thompson, Denham.; Beiller, Bayard.; Williams, Jessie.; Winter, William.; Young, Rida Johnson.; Abbey Theatre (Dublin, Ireland); Orpheum Theatre (San Francisco, Calif.); Pasadena Playhouse (Pasadena, Calif.); Moscow Art Theatre.; Teck Theatre (Buffalo, NY); Harry Lofgren Minstrel Show.
Collection Contents
- Series 1: 19th Century American and British Stage
  - #565- "Compiled June '93 by Bessie McJohnston, Kentucky"1890-93 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    American theatre bills, 1890-93
  - #573 - pictorial of American Shakespearean actors1895-96 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - #578 - compiled by Elizabeth Saunders1909 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    mostly articles, etc. on Joseph Jefferson, American stage actor, 1880s
  - #104 - "22 old newspapers, minstrel shows, ads; also museums and theatres"1862-1869 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - #102 - "34 old newspapers, 1875-1880" (Box 1, Folder 5)
    The Mirror and American from Manchester, New Hampshire; minstrel show ads
  - #1a - tiny minstrel scrapbook (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - #16 - theatre clippings, programs, and comments, (Amer.)1883 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - #537 - "McVicker's Book of the Play";1876-77 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Programs
  - #6 - Vol. 1; clippings of performances at the Leland Opera House 1876-78 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - #6- Vol. 2; clippings of performances at the Leland Opera House1878-79 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - #32 - scrapbook of Adelaide Merton c. 1892-98 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Poems, clippings of theatre reviews and pictures of actors
  - #15 - "Card Album"1885 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Newspaper clippings, reviews
  - #93 - scrapbook of Mr. Wilson Barrett c. 1898-1900 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Theatre reviews
  - #544 - Theatre programs, newspaper clippings on theatre, and miscellaneous.ca.1870s (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - #61 - scrapbook on American actor Edwin Booth 1893 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - #12 - oversized volume - American theatre1870s (Box 2a, Folder 1)
- Series 2: Photos of 19th & Early 20th C. American and British Actors
  - #35 - photo album of women in costume 1870s-80s (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - #77 - embossed leather album; 19th C. American actors (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - #76 - black leather album; 19th C. American actors (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - #75 - "Actors"; 19th C. stage and opera personalities (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - #31 - oversized album - etchings of American 19th C. Shakespearean actors (Box 3a, Folder 1)
  - #3 - one of two scrapbooks bought by Sam Stark from Alice Burtis, Muskogee, OK (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - #5 - famous actors, actresses of 19th C. American stage (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - #50 - British and American actors (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - #78 - photos taken and developed by a Mr. Dorsaz; American theatre companies, 19th C. c.1884-88 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - #103 - stars of the 19th C. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - #95 - American stage actors, actresses; c. 1900-1905 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - #96 - celebrities, 1900-1920s, including early cinema (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - #46 - elaborate embossed leather album with index; American stage actors1888-93 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - #47 - more photos, same period, American stage actors (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - #48 - Ellen Terry's (British actress) family photo album (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - #1 - "The Theatre, England, 1878-81" photo album (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Series 3: American Stage, c. l900-l920s
  - #49 - American and British theatre performances 1899-1909 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - #59 - Irish theatre; Abbey Theatre clippings, programs1907 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - #94 - San Francisco theatre programs, April 1905 - April 1906; a few Seattle programs1905-1906 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - #2 - programs, clippings c. 1904; several from the Teck Theatre, Buffalo NYc.1904 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - no # - charred gray cloth binder; photos & pictures of American actresses in the Burr McIntosh Monthly, January 1908; Theatre Magazine, January 19191908, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - #101 - "Mrs. Leland Stanford Lathrop's Scrapbook"; programs from California (esp. San Francisco) theatres (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - #117 - pictures of plays from the periodical "New York Dramatic Mirror." 1916-17 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - #569 - clippings of pictures and playbills, "American Stage."c. 1904-1916 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - #574 - photos of famous actors; "Lamb's All-Star Gambol." c.l909 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - #8 - Vol. 1; clippings, magazine photos from "The Stage"; also some playbills.1872 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - #8 - Vol. 2; clippings, magazine photos from "The Stage"; also some playbills. 1872-83 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - #8 - Vol. 3; clippings, magazine photos from "The Stage"; also some playbills.1907 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - #80 - programs, pictures from New York City theatre performances. 1901-09 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - #81 - programs, pictures from New York City theatre performances. 1906-07 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - #82 - programs, pictures from New York City theatre performances.1907-09 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - #83 - programs, pictures from New York City theatre performances.1909-10 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - #84 - programs, pictures from New York City theatre performances.1911 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - #85 - programs, pictures from New York City theatre performances.1912-26 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - #86 - programs, pictures from New York City theatre performances,1929-30; "Plays I Have Seen" (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - #30 - "Theatre Record" c. 1903-08; London and British productions in New York (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - #69 - San Francisco theatre programs.1901-1902 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - #543 - vaudeville, light theatre programs, San Francisco theatres; several from the Orpheumc. 1906-1911 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - #542 - vaudeville in San Francisco.1911-1914 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - #536 - programs from Boston theatres.1896-97 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - #534 - programs from Boston theatres.1910 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - #535 - programs from Boston theatres.1911 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - #97 - theatre record of Charles R. Hector; "St. James Theatre, Boston Stock Company, Season 1921-22" (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - #98 - theatre record of Charles R. Hector; "St. James Theatre, Boston Stock Company, Season 1922-23" (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - #99 - theatre record of Charles R. Hector; "St. James Theatre, Boston Stock Company, Season 1923-24" (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - #100 - theatre record of Charles R. Hector; "St. James Theatre, Boston Stock Company, Season 1924-25" (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - #87 - "Theatre Vol. V, 1920"; programs and issues of "Phillybound," all from Philadelphia. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - #87 - "Theatre Vol. VI, 1921-22"; programs and issues of "Phillybound," all from Philadelphia. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - #89 - "Theatre Vol. VII, 1922-23, 1924-25"; programs and issues of "Phillybound," all from Philadelphia. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - #90 - "Theatre Vol. VIII, 1926-27"; programs and issues of "Phillybound," all from Philadelphia. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - #91 - "Theatre, January - August 1928"; programs and issues of "Phillybound," all from Philadelphia. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - #92 - "Theatre, September - December 1928"; programs and issues of "Phillybound," all from Philadelphia. (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Series 4: American Film, Silents to 1940s-50s
  - no # - film scrapbook, "Marie Antoinette," starring Norma Shearer and Tyrone Power. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - no # - "Charles Boyer's True Life Story" (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - no # - "Cinema Stars Vol. 1," put together by Arthur and Elaine at The Deanery. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - no # - "Cinema Stars Vol. 2" put together by Arthur and Elaine at The Deanery. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - no # - "Cinema Stars Vol. 3" put together by Arthur and Elaine at The Deanery. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - no # - "Cinema Stars Vol. 4"; put together by Arthur and Elaine at The Deanery; plus Carole Lombard's life story. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - no # - "Cinema Stars Vol. 5" put together by Arthur and Elaine at The Deanery. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - #38 - "Paramount Pictures: Jewels of the Silent Stage" (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - #4 - "I Pagliacci"; homemade scrapbook of silent film stars. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - #7 - "People Who Cast Bright Shadows"; silent film stars. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - #9 - "Scenes from Productions Starring Richard Barthelmess" (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - #45 - "Miscellaneous"; history of early films; various articles c. 1907 and correspondence c. 1950. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - #34 - Fox Film Corporation scrapbook; silent film directors and stars. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - #12a - scrapbook of child star Jackie Cooper, "In my own play, 'My Boy"; to his friend Henry G. Meyer. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - #10 - "Dream Folks" picture album of silent film stars. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - #29 oversized film scrapbook - purple and gold "Krasiva Metals Fall & Winter 1938" scrapbook; pictorial of American movie stars, l9l0s-40s. (Box 10a, Folder 1)
  - #37 oversized film scrapbook - Claude Allister scrapbook (see Box 16 for more). (Box 10a, Folder 2)
  - #107 oversized film scrapbook - large wooden case holding a leather scrapbook; Marie Dressler's 62nd birthday. (Box 10a, Folder 3)
- Series 5: 20th C. American Theatre
  - #572 - programs from performances in San Francisco, Berkeley, and other Bay Area theatres, c. 1920-1932 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - #19 - Journal of F. Gasebekeuchtung; "Theatre Magazine." 1921-22 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - #20 - a scrapbook of ballet dancers Yvonne Georgi and Harald Kreutzberg, c. l930s; programs from San Francisco (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - #74 - drama reviews, New York Times. 1936-38 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - #111 - theatre programs and reviews; Los Angeles, Hollywood, Pasadena Playhouse, UCLA, USC; 1926-34; (Ralph Shran) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - #112 - theatre programs and reviews; Los Angeles, Hollywood, Pasadena Playhouse, UCLA, USC; September 1935 - September 1935 (Ralph Shran) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - #113 - theatre programs and reviews; Los Angeles, Hollywood, Pasadena Playhouse, UCLA, USC; September 1935 - September 1936 (Ralph Shran) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - #114 - theatre programs and reviews; Los Angeles, Hollywood, Pasadena Playhouse, UCLA, USC; September 1936 - August 1937; also Santa Barbara, Palo Alto, San Francisco (Ralph Shran) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - #115 - theatre programs and reviews; Los Angeles, Hollywood, Pasadena Playhouse, UCLA, USC; September 1937 - August 1938 (Ralph Shran) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - #116 - theatre programs and reviews; Los Angeles, Hollywood, Pasadena Playhouse, UCLA, USC; September 1938 - December 1939 (Ralph Shran) (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - #79 - Vol. 1; censorship in motion pictures, entertainment; information, correspondences, etc.; 1920s-30s (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - #79 - Vol. 2; censorship in motion pictures, entertainment; information, correspondences, etc.; 1920s-30s, 1927-36 specifically (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - #70 - Vol. 1; 1930s-40s film and stage stars, American and British; lots on Noel Coward and his productions (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - #70 - Vol. 2; 1930s-40s film and stage stars, American and British; lots on Noel Coward and his productions (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - #70 - Vol. 3; 1930s-40s film and stage stars, American and British; lots on Noel Coward and his productions (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - #14 - "Henry Lofgren Minstrel Show Clippings" 1930s-40s (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - #17 - "Theatre"; clippings, some programs 1930s-40s (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - #60 - "Moscow Art Theatre 50th Anniversary" photo album (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - #105 - clippings about minstrel shows and [original text missing]c. 1933-45. (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Series 6: Personal Collections of Photos, Clippings, Programs, Etc.; American Theatre and Film History
  - #40 - columns by Patterson Greene, theatre and film commentator, Los Angeles Herald Examiner.1920s-50s (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - #41 - columns by Patterson Greene, theatre and film commentator, Los Angeles Herald Examiner.1960-62 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - #42 - columns by Patterson Greene, theatre and film commentator, Los Angeles Herald Examiner. 1963-64 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - #43 - columns by Patterson Greene, theatre and film commentator, Los Angeles Herald Examiner.1964-65 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - #51 - columns by Patterson Greene, theatre and film commentator, Los Angeles Herald Examiner.1966 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - #52 - columns by Patterson Greene, theatre and film commentator, Los Angeles Herald Examiner.1967 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - #53 - columns by Patterson Greene, theatre and film commentator, Los Angeles Herald Examiner.1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - #54 - columns by Patterson Greene, theatre and film commentator, Los Angeles Herald Examiner.1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - #55 - columns by Patterson Greene, theatre and film commentator, Los Angeles Herald Examiner.1965-1966 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - #56 - columns by Patterson Greene, theatre and film commentator, Los Angeles Herald Examiner.1966-67 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - #58 oversized photo album (see box l0a) - photographs of American theatres (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - #68 - scrapbook on Anton Chekov (1860-1904) "for the centenary of his birth" (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - #108 - newspaper clippings, several obituaries of theatre celebrities. 1937-47 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - #109 - theatre clippings, especially "Show Boat" ads, programs, pictures, and minstrel stuff.1947-48 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - #110 - "Old Man River" and other showboat clippings.l940s (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - #18 - New York City theatres, photos and history. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - #39 - clippings about California theatres. 1900-30s (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - #563 - theatre history and obituaries, pictures, etc. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - #44 - scrapbook of early film and American stage.l9l0s (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - #570 - "Margaret Storey: Programs, Photos"; very eclectic scrapbook; most programs from the 1920s (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - #26 - scrapbook of Thomas Lindsay; clippings on Damon Runyon and various pieces of correspondence. 1941-42 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - #21 - "Down Memory Lane with Tom Lindsay"; film and drama newspaper columns (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - #562 - "Magicians' Programs." 1920s-50s (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - #107 - American prize fights, 19th and early 20th C. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - #11 - a photo album of Sam Stark's; some film scripts; also, film history bits and newspaper clippings. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - #57 - scrapbook of John Stein, press agent and presenter; programs, clippings, autographed photos. (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Series 7: Theatre and Film Star Scrapbooks, 19th & 20th C., American and British
  - #1 - Maud Adams (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - #2 - Viola Allen (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - #2a - Claude Allister (manila envelope of photos, etc.) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - #36 - Claude Allister (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - #3 - Margaret Anglin (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - #4 - The Barrymores (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - #70 - Vols. 1-3, the Barrymores (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - #4a - Blanche Bates (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - #5 - Jack Benny (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - #6 - Vol. 1; Sarah Bernhardt (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - #6 - Vol. 2; Sarah Bernhardt (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - #7 - Billie Burke (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - #8 - James Cagney (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - #9 - Irene Vernon Castle (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - #10 - Charlie Chaplin (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - #11 - George M. Cohan (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - #12 - Ronald Coleman (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - #13 - Bette Davis (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - #14 - Marie Dressier (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - #15 - The Drews (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - #16 - Gertrude and Maxine Elliott (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - #17 - Douglas Fairbanks (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - #18 - Geraldine Farrar (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - #19 - Minnie Madden Fiske (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - #20 - Pauline Frederick (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - #21 - Trixie Friganza (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - #22 - Clark Gable (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - #23 - Dorothy and Lillian Gish (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - #24 - Giida Gray (from Imhof's collection) (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - #25 - Anna Held (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - #26 - Mary Mannering (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - #27 - Julia Marlowe (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - #28 - Edna May (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - #29 - Victor Moore (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - #30 - Ana Nazimora (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - #31 - Mary Pickford (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - #32 - Tyrone Power (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - #33 - Blanche Ring (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - #34 - Lillian Russell (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - #35 - Frances Starr (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - #36 - Anita Stewart (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - #37 - Gloria Swanson (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - #38 - Constance and Norma Talmadge (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - #39 - Eva Tanguay (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - #40 - Fay Templeton (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - #41 - Ellen Terrj (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - #42 - Rudolph Valentino (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - #43 - Weber C. Fields (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - #44 - Mae West (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Series 8: American Stage Personalities, l900-l930s
  - #1 - George Ade, Louis Anspacker, Paul Armstrong, Frederick Ballard, Phillip Barry, Tom Barry, Philip Bartholomae, Dion Boucicault (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - #2 - George H. Broadhurst, Porter Emerson Browne, Thompson Buchanan, Anne Caidwell, Edward Childs Carpenter, Joseph I. C. Clarke, George N. Cohan (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - #3 - Frank Craven, Rachel Crothers, Owen Davis, Richard H.Davis, William C. DeMille, Lee Wilson Dodd, Edith Ellis (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - #4 - Clyde Fitch, James Forbes, Eleanor Gates (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - #5 - William Gillette, Jules E. Goodman, Frederick Hutton, George Hazelton, Charles Hoyt, Avery Hopwood, Sidney Howard, Bronson Howard (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - #6 - Rupert Hughes, William Hurlburt, Charles R. Kennedy, Charles Kenyon, Paul Kester, Charles Klein (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - #7 - Charles Klein, Edward Knoblauch, Theodore Kramer, John L.Long, Percy MacKaye (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - #8 - C.S. N. McClellan, J. H. Manners, Margaret Mayo, Roi C.Megrue, George Middleton, Langdon Mitchell, James Montgomery, William Vaughn Moody, Carlyle Moore (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - #9 - Martha Morton, Charles Nirdlinger, Lottie B. Parker, Joseph Patterson, Edward Paulson, Harry Paulton, Josephine Peabody, Edward Peple, Channing Pollack (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - #10 - Eugene Presbrey, James Reid, Sydney Rosenfeld, Edwin Royle, N. C. Ryley, Theodore B. Sayre, George Scarborough, Edgar Selwyn, G. B. Shaw (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - #11 - G.B. Shaw, Edward Sheldon, Louis E. Shipman, Harry Smith, Winchell Smith (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - #12 - Evelyn Sutherland, Booth Tarkington, Charles Taylor, Albert Thomas, Augustus Thomas, Denham Thompson (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - #13 - Richard Tully, Bayard Beiller, Eugene Walter, Jessie Williams, William Winter (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - #14 - Rida Johnson Young (Box 19, Folder 14)